nuffnang.com.sg 2012-10-18

# Nuffnang Singapore | Asia Pacific's First Blog Advertising Community

Nuffnang Pte. Ltd., operator of the Nuffnang.com.sg website, (" **Nuffnang.com.sg** ") provides an online advertising sale and display service for publishers of Blogs (the " **Service** "). We sell " **Advertiser(s)** " the right to place advertisements (" **Ad(s)** ") via the Service into a Javascript (" **Adstrip** ") that is then sent to and displayed on one or more web sites of our network of Blog publishers (" **Publisher(s)** ") and managed by such Publishers. The Service runs on software developed by Nuffnang Pte. Ltd., its subsidiaries and third party contractors.

* _COLLECTION OF INFORMATION_

If you are an Advertiser or a Publisher, during your dealings with Nuffnang.com.sg, Nuffnang.com.sg may request any information related to your website and/or blog and your use of Nuffnang.com.sg’s ads. If you provide such information to Nuffnang.com.sg, Nuffnang.com.sg may collect and store such personal information. Nuffnang.com.sg may collect your email addresses, mailing and billing address, IP address, information about your web site, including but not limited to your site’s page impressions, Nuffnang.com.sg prices and data about your readers both current and historical. Nuffnang.com.sg will collect information regarding your activities through the Service. Nuffnang.com.sg will collect any comments you may send to Nuffnang.com.sg and any information you may post to the Nuffnang.com.sg site or a Publisher site. Nuffnang.com.sg may also collect information through the use of Cookies (as defined below). Nuffnang.com.sg collects personal information when you: (1) register with Nuffnang.com.sg to become a Publisher or Advertiser, (2) provide comments or submit a problem to Nuffnang.com.sg or a Nuffnang.com.sg Publisher, (3) request information from Nuffnang.com.sg and provide your name or return contact information, or (4) respond to special offers, contests or surveys. As part of the registration process, you may be asked to provide contact information and other personally identifying information.

* _COOKIES_

"Cookies" are data files that may be downloaded to your computer when you visit the Nuffnang.com.sg site or a Publisher site and permit the Nuffnang.com.sg server to identify your browser whenever you interact with the Nuffnang.com.sg site or a Nuffnang.com.sg Publisher site. Nuffnang.com.sg uses cookies to recognize repeat visits by users of its Service and to collect information about its users' interactions with the Services. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to streamline your experiences using the Services and to report such information to Publishers and Advertisers. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to optimize the features of the Services. In some cases, you may not be able to access Services if cookies are disabled.

* _EXTERNAL LINKS_

As a part of the Services, Nuffnang.com.sg provides links to web sites operated by third parties. Nuffnang.com.sg is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party sites.

* _EXTERNAL SURVEYS_

Nuffnang.com.sg collects information through reader surveys published on blogs under the Nuffnang.com.sg network. Nuffnang.com.sg retains the right to analyze, process, use and share this information with advertisers in order to segment the audience of each blog in the hope of feeding relevant ads to blog readers.

* _USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION_

  * **If you are a Publisher** , we may share information about your Site, including but not limited to page impressions, site traffic, prices, information on publisher site readers/users and readership with Advertisers, Publishers or Users. We may share your e-mail address with other Publishers and your traffic data with the Publisher who enrolled you into using the Service.
  * **If you are an Advertiser** , we may disclosure your contact information and e-mail address to Publishers on whose Sites you have ordered advertisements.
  * **If you are a User** , we may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information about you with Publishers or Advertisers such as the number of users who visit a Publisher site or the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. Further, you are encouraged to review the privacy policies of the Publishers that you access. You should contact Publishers directly and review their privacy policies should you have questions concerning their use of your information.
  * **Other Disclosures**. Nuffnang.com.sg may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or if Nuffnang.com.sg has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to protect and/or defend the rights and interests of Nuffnang.com.sg. Nuffnang.com.sg may, as permitted by applicable law, disclose your personally identifiable information to Publishers or Advertisers, or third parties in connection with an investigation of fraud, infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity and you expressly authorize Nuffnang.com.sg to make such disclosures.
  * **Domestic and International Use.** All personally identifying information collected by Nuffnang.com.sg may be used in Singapore, Malaysia, Philippines, Thailand, Australia and China or if the Services are undertaken by Nuffnang.com.sg for a foreign Publisher or Advertiser, such information may be transferred to that Publisher or Advertiser outside of Singapore, Malaysia, Philippines, Thailand, Australia, and China and you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.
  * **Merger or Acquisition.** If Nuffnang Pte. Ltd. is merged or acquired by another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to such entity as a part of the merger or acquisition.

* _REVIEW AND MODIFICATIONS TO YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION_

If you are a Publisher or Advertiser, you may add, modify or update your email address, name, mailing address and other contact information by accessing the “My Account” page on the Service. It is your responsibility to ensure that the information you have on Nuffnang.com.sg is the most up-to-date information as possible. Nuffnang.com.sg may retain transactional history in order to document a transaction you may have had with a Nuffnang.com.sg Publisher or Advertiser. You should contact the Publisher or Advertiser directly in order to access, modify or update your personal information with them.

* _SECURITY_

Nuffnang.com.sg stores all information including personally identifiable information obtained through registration securely and considers it part of the assets of its business. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Nuffnang.com.sg has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, data security is a constantly evolving art and science. You should consider any communication that you transmit to Nuffnang.com.sg (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that Nuffnang.com.sg will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.
